Register of the William Patrick Clark papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Post-Government Service File, 1985-2008
  - Miscellaneous speeches and writings
    - Statement re California Supreme Court decision on parental consent for abortions, 1997 August 7 (Box-folder 132: 11)
      Typescript and draft
    - "Ronald Reagan, Lifeguard,", 2000 June 25 (Box-folder 132: 12)
      Typescript
    - "President Reagan and the Wall,", undated (Box-folder 132: 13)
    - Miscellaneous speeches and drafts, undated (Box-folder 132: 14)
    - Speeches by others for speech file background use (Box-folder 132: 15)
    - Printed matter and miscellaneous background material for speech file use (Box-folder 132: 16)
  - Chronological correspondence (outgoing and some incoming letters)
    - 1985 February (Box-folder 133: 1)
    - 1985 March (Box-folder 133: 2)
    - 1985 April (Box-folder 133: 3)
    - 1985 May (Box-folder 133: 4)
    - 1985 June (Box-folder 133: 5)
    - 1985 July (Box-folder 133: 6)
    - 1985 August (Box-folder 133: 7)
    - 1985 September (Box-folder 133: 8)
    - 1985 October (Box-folder 133: 9)
    - 1985 November (Box-folder 133: 10)
    - 1985 December (Box-folder 133: 11)
    - 1985 Christmas gift acknowledgments (Box-folder 133: 12)
    - 1986 January (Box-folder 133: 13)
    - 1986 February (Box-folder 133: 14)
    - 1986 March (Box-folder 134: 1)
    - 1986 April (Box-folder 134: 2)
    - 1986 May (Box-folder 134: 3)
    - 1986 June (Box-folder 134: 4)
    - 1986 July (Box-folder 134: 5)
    - 1986 August (Box-folder 134: 6)
    - 1986 September (Box-folder 134: 7)
    - 1986 October (Box-folder 134: 8)
    - 1986 November (Box-folder 134: 9)
    - 1986 December (Box-folder 134: 10)
    - 1987 January (Box-folder 134: 11)
    - 1987 February (Box-folder 134: 12)
    - 1987 March (Box-folder 135: 1)
    - 1987 April (Box-folder 135: 2)
    - 1987 May (Box-folder 135: 3)
    - 1987 June (Box-folder 135: 4)
    - 1987 July (Box-folder 135: 5)
    - 1987 August (Box-folder 135: 6)
    - 1987 September (Box-folder 135: 7)
    - 1987 October (Box-folder 135: 8)
    - 1987 November (Box-folder 135: 9)
    - 1987 December (Box-folder 135: 10)
    - 1988 January (Box-folder 135: 11)
    - 1988 February (Box-folder 135: 12)
    - 1988 March (Box-folder 135: 13)
    - 1988 April (Box-folder 135: 14)
    - 1988 May (Box-folder 135: 15)
    - 1988 June (Box-folder 135: 16)
    - 1988 July (Box-folder 135: 17)
    - 1988 August (Box-folder 136: 1)
    - 1988 September (Box-folder 136: 2)
    - 1988 October (Box-folder 136: 3)
    - 1988 November (Box-folder 136: 4)
    - 1988 December (Box-folder 136: 5)
    - 1989 January (Box-folder 136: 6)
    - 1989 February (Box-folder 136: 7)
    - 1989 March (Box-folder 136: 8)
    - 1989 April (Box-folder 136: 9)
    - 1989 May (Box-folder 137: 1)
    - 1989 June (Box-folder 137: 2)
    - 1989 July (Box-folder 137: 3)
    - 1989 August (Box-folder 137: 4)
    - 1989 September (Box-folder 137: 5)
    - 1989 October (Box-folder 137: 6)
    - 1989 November (Box-folder 137: 7)
    - 1989 December (Box-folder 137: 8)
    - 1990 January (Box-folder 137: 9)
    - 1990 February (Box-folder 137: 10)
    - 1990 March (Box-folder 137: 11)
    - 1990 April (Box-folder 138: 1)
    - 1990 May (Box-folder 138: 2)
    - 1990 June (Box-folder 138: 3)
    - 1990 July (Box-folder 138: 4)
    - 1990 August (Box-folder 138: 5)
    - 1990 September (Box-folder 138: 6)
    - 1990 October (Box-folder 138: 7)
    - 1990 November (Box-folder 138: 8)
    - 1990 December (Box-folder 138: 9)
    - 1995 (Box-folder 138: 10)
    - 1996 (Box-folder 138: 11)
    - 1997 (Box-folder 138: 12)
    - 1998 (Box-folder 139: 1)
    - 1999 (Box-folder 139: 2)
    - 2000 (Box-folder 139: 3)
    - 2001 (Box-folder 139: 4)
    - 2002 (Box-folder 139: 5)
  - 1985 alphabetical correspondence
    - A (Box-folder 139: 6)
    - Abrams, Elliott (Box-folder 139: 7)
    - Annenberg, Walter H. (Box-folder 139: 8)
    - B (Box-folder 139: 9)
    - Bandar, Prince (Saudi Arabian ambassador) (Box-folder 139: 10)
    - Buchanan, Patrick (Box-folder 139: 11)
    - Bush, George (Box-folder 139: 12)
    - C (Box-folder 139: 13)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box-folder 139: 14)
    - Chiang, Ching-kuo (president of Taiwan) (Box-folder 139: 15)
    - Chun, Doo Hwan (president of South Korea) (Box-folder 139: 16)
    - D (Box-folder 139: 17)
    - Deukmejian, George (Box-folder 139: 18)
    - Donovan, Raymond J. (Box-folder 139: 19)
    - Drury, Allen (Box-folder 139: 20)
    - E (Box-folder 139: 21)
    - F (Box-folder 139: 22)
    - FitzGerald, Garrett (prime minister of Ireland) (Box-folder 139: 23)
    - G (Box-folder 140: 1)
    - Goldwater, Barry (Box-folder 140: 2)
    - H (Box-folder 140: 3)
    - Haig, Alexander (Box-folder 140: 4)
    - Harmer, John L. (Box-folder 140: 5)
    - Haslauer, Wilfried (Box-folder 140: 6)
    - Hersh, Seymour (Box-folder 140: 7)
    - Hewitt, William A. (Box-folder 140: 8)
    - Hodel, Donald P. (Box-folder 140: 9)
    - J (Box-folder 140: 10)
    - Javits, Jacob K. (Box-folder 140: 11)
    - Jordan, Amos A. (Box-folder 140: 12)
    - K (Box-folder 140: 13)
    - Klestil, Thomas (Austrian ambassador) (Box-folder 140: 14)
    - L (Box-folder 140: 15)
    - Lefever, Ernest W. (Box-folder 140: 16)
    - Lew, Byong Hiong (South Korean ambassador) (Box-folder 140: 17)
    - Lewis, Drew (Box-folder 140: 18)
    - M (Box-folder 140: 19)
    - McCoy, Tidal W. (Box-folder 140: 20)
    - Meese, Edwin, III (Box-folder 140: 21)
    - Menges, Constantine C. (Box-folder 140: 22)
    - Middendorf, J. William, II (Box-folder 140: 23)
    - Morlion, Andrew Felix (Box-folder 140: 24)
    - Mosk, Stanley (Box-folder 140: 25)
    - N (Box-folder 141: 1)
    - Neumann, Robert G. (Box-folder 141: 2)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box-folder 141: 3)
    - O (Box-folder 141: 4)
    - Okawara, Yoshio (Japanese ambassador) (Box-folder 141: 5)
    - O'Sullivan, Tadhg (Irish ambassador) (Box-folder 141: 6)
    - P (Box-folder 141: 7)
    - Pendley, Wiliam Perry (Box-folder 141: 8)
    - Quinn, Arthur Lee (Box-folder 141: 9)
    - R (Box-folder 141: 10)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 141: 11)
    - Regan, Donald T. (Box-folder 141: 12)
    - Ritchotte, John F. (Box-folder 141: 13)
    - Rostropovich, Mstislav (Box-folder 141: 14)
    - S (Box-folder 141: 15)
    - Shultz, George P. (Box-folder 141: 16)
    - T (Box-folder 141: 17)
    - Theberge, James D. (Box-folder 141: 18)
    - Tuttle, Robert (Box-folder 141: 19)
    - V (Box-folder 141: 20)
    - W (Box-folder 141: 21)
    - Weinberger, Caspar (Box-folder 141: 22)
    - Wick, Charles Z. (Box-folder 141: 23)
    - Willard, Richard K. (Box-folder 141: 24)
    - Wilson, Pete (Box-folder 141: 25)
    - Z (Box-folder 141: 26)
  - 1986 alphabetical correspondence
    - A (Box-folder 141: 27)
    - Alexander, Lamar (Box-folder 141: 28)
    - Avedisian, Armen G. (Box-folder 142: 1)
    - B (Box-folder 142: 2)
    - Bandar, Prince (Saudi Arabian ambassador) (Box-folder 142: 3)
    - C (Box-folder 142: 4)
    - Casey, William J. (Box-folder 142: 5)
    - Chapin, Roger (Box-folder 142: 6)
    - Chien, Frederick F. (Box-folder 142: 7)
    - Cotton, John W. (Box-folder 142: 8)
    - D (Box-folder 142: 9)
    - Davis, Jeffrey C. (Box-folder 142: 10)
    - Drury, Allen (Box-folder 142: 11)
    - E (Box-folder 142: 12)
    - F (Box-folder 142: 13)
    - FitzGerald, Garrett (prime minister of Ireland) (Box-folder 142: 14)
    - G (Box-folder 142: 15)
    - Gavin, John (Box-folder 142: 16)
    - H (Box-folder 142: 17)
    - Hanes, Roger W. (Box-folder 142: 18)
    - Harmer, John L. (Box-folder 142: 19)
    - Hassan II, King of Morocco (Box-folder 142: 20)
    - Herrington, John S. (Box-folder 142: 21)
    - I (Box-folder 143: 1)
    - Ikle, Fred C. (Box-folder 143: 2)
    - J (Box-folder 143: 3)
    - Jordan, Amos A. (Box-folder 143: 4)
    - K (Box-folder 143: 5)
    - Kelly, Ned (Box-folder 143: 6)
    - Kirkpatrick, Jeane J. (Box-folder 143: 7)
    - Klestil, Thomas (Austrian ambassador) (Box-folder 143: 8)
    - L (Box-folder 143: 9)
    - Lenczowski, George (Box-folder 143: 10)
    - Levada, William J. (Box-folder 143: 11)
    - M (Box-folder 143: 12)
    - McFarlane, Robert C. (Box-folder 143: 13)
    - Meese, Edwin, III (Box-folder 143: 14)
    - Middendorf, J. William, II (Box-folder 143: 15)
    - N (Box-folder 143: 16)
    - Neumann, Robert G. (Box-folder 143: 17)
    - O (Box-folder 143: 18)
    - P (Box-folder 143: 19)
    - Packard, David (Box-folder 143: 20)
    - Pendley, William Perry (Box-folder 143: 21)
    - Perez, Carlos (Box-folder 143: 22)
    - Petrignani, Rinaldo (Italian ambassador) (Box-folder 143: 23)
    - Poindexter, John (Box-folder 143: 24)
    - R (Box-folder 143: 25)
    - Ramadan, Taha Y. (first deputy prime minister of Iraq) (Box-folder 143: 26)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 143: 27)
    - Robinson, Gilbert A. (Box-folder 143: 28)
    - Robinson, Roger W., Jr. (Box-folder 143: 29)
    - Rossides, Eugene T. (Box-folder 143: 30)
    - S (Box-folder 144: 1)
    - T (Box-folder 144: 2)
    - Tambs, Lewis A. (Box-folder 144: 3)
    - Tappan, David S., Jr. (Box-folder 144: 4)
    - Theberge, James D. (Box-folder 144: 5)
    - V (Box-folder 144: 6)
    - W (Box-folder 144: 7)
    - Weinberger, Caspar (Box-folder 144: 8)
    - Y (Box-folder 144: 9)
  - 1987 alphabetical correspondence
    - A (Box-folder 144: 10)
    - Abshire, David M. (Box-folder 144: 11)
    - Agnew, Harold M. (Box-folder 144: 12)
    - Aziz, Tariq (Iraqi foreign minister) (Box-folder 144: 13)
    - B (Box-folder 144: 14)
    - Bandar, Prince (Saudi Arabian ambassador) (Box-folder 144: 15)
    - Brown, Harold (Box-folder 144: 16)
    - Brzezinski, Zbigniew (Box-folder 144: 17)
    - C (Box-folder 144: 18)
    - Carlucci, Frank C. (Box-folder 144: 19)
    - Chien, Frederick F. (Box-folder 144: 20)
    - Crozier, Brian (Box-folder 144: 21)
    - Culvahouse, Arthur B., Jr. (Box-folder 144: 22)
    - D (Box-folder 144: 23)
    - Donlon, Sean (Irish foreign minister) (Box-folder 144: 24)
    - E (Box-folder 144: 25)
    - F (Box-folder 144: 26)
    - FitzGerald, Garrett (prime minister of Ireland) (Box-folder 144: 27)
    - G (Box-folder 145: 1)
    - Gavin, John (Box-folder 145: 2)
    - Gerami, Mehdi (Box-folder 145: 3)
    - H (Box-folder 145: 4)
    - Hammer, Armand (Box-folder 145: 5)
    - Herrington, John S. (Box-folder 145: 6)
    - Hodel, Donald P. (Box-folder 145: 7)
    - Horowitz, Michael J. (Box-folder 145: 8)
    - J (Box-folder 145: 9)
    - K (Box-folder 145: 10)
    - Kennedy, Anthony M. (Box-folder 145: 11)
    - Klestil, Thomas (Austrian ambassador) (Box-folder 145: 12)
    - L (Box-folder 145: 13)
    - Lenczowski, George (Box-folder 145: 14)
    - Levine, Richard B. (Box-folder 145: 15)
    - Lord, Cary (Box-folder 145: 16)
    - M (Box-folder 145: 17)
    - McCain, John (Box-folder 145: 18)
    - McCormack, Richard T. (Box-folder 145: 19)
    - McFarlane, Robert C. (Box-folder 145: 20)
    - Matsunaga, Nobuo (Japanese ambassador) (Box-folder 145: 21)
    - Mayer, Jane (Box-folder 145: 22)
    - Menges, Constantine C. (Box-folder 145: 23)
    - Middendorf, J. William, II (Box-folder 146: 1)
    - Morrill, William A. (Box-folder 146: 2)
    - Morris, Edmund (Box-folder 146: 3)
    - N (Box-folder 146: 4)
    - Nazer, Hisham M. (Saudi Arabian minister of petroleum and mineral resources) (Box-folder 146: 5)
    - Nofziger, Lyn (Box-folder 146: 6)
    - O (Box-folder 146: 7)
    - O'Connor, Sandra Day (Box-folder 146: 8)
    - P (Box-folder 146: 9)
    - Packard, David (Box-folder 146: 10)
    - Perez, Carlos (Box-folder 146: 11)
    - R (Box-folder 146: 12)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 146: 13)
    - Rossides, Eugene T. (Box-folder 146: 14)
    - Rostropovich, Mstislav (Box-folder 146: 15)
    - S (Box-folder 146: 16)
    - Sarasin, Arsa (Thai ambassador) (Box-folder 146: 17)
    - Sigur, Gaston (Box-folder 146: 18)
    - T (Box-folder 146: 19)
    - Tower, John (Box-folder 146: 20)
    - U (Box-folder 146: 21)
    - W (Box-folder 146: 22)
    - Weinberger, Caspar (Box-folder 146: 23)
    - Whittlesey, Faith Ryan (Box-folder 146: 24)
    - Wigg, David G. (Box-folder 146: 25)
    - Williamson, Richard (Box-folder 146: 26)
    - Y (Box-folder 146: 27)
    - Yeutter, Clayton (Box-folder 146: 28)
    - Z (Box-folder 146: 29)
  - 1988 alphabetical correspondence
    - A (Box-folder 146: 30)
    - Armstrong, Anne (Box-folder 146: 31)
    - B (Box-folder 146: 32)
    - Baker, Howard H., Jr. (Box-folder 146: 33)
    - Bandar, Prince (Saudi Arabian ambassador) (Box-folder 146: 34)
    - Bishirjian, Richard J. (Box-folder 147: 1)
    - Buckley, William F., Jr. (Box-folder 147: 2)
    - Bush, George (Box-folder 147: 3)
    - C (Box-folder 147: 4)
    - Carlucci, Frank C. (Box-folder 147: 5)
    - Chiang, Ching-kuo (Box-folder 147: 6)
    - Chien, Frederick F. (Box-folder 147: 7)
    - D (Box-folder 147: 8)
    - Duberstein, Kenneth (Box-folder 147: 9)
    - E (Box-folder 147: 10)
    - F (Box-folder 147: 11)
    - Feulner, Edwin J., Jr. (Box-folder 147: 12)
    - G (Box-folder 147: 13)
    - Gannon, Francis X. (Box-folder 147: 14)
    - H (Box-folder 147: 15)
    - Hoess, Friedrich (Austrian ambassador) (Box-folder 147: 16)
    - I (Box-folder 147: 17)
    - J (Box-folder 147: 18)
    - K (Box-folder 147: 19)
    - Kemp, Jack (Box-folder 147: 20)
    - Kim, Kyung-Won (South Korean ambassador) (Box-folder 147: 21)
    - L (Box-folder 147: 22)
    - Lane, L. W., Jr. (Box-folder 147: 23)
    - M (Box-folder 147: 24)
    - Menges, Constantine C. (Box-folder 147: 25)
    - Mosk, Stanley (Box-folder 147: 26)
    - N (Box-folder 147: 27)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box-folder 147: 28)
    - O (Box-folder 147: 29)
    - P (Box-folder 147: 30)
    - Perez, Carlos (Box-folder 147: 31)
    - R (Box-folder 147: 32)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 147: 33)
    - Rockefeller, David (Box-folder 147: 34)
    - Rostropovich, Mstislav (Box-folder 147: 35)
    - Rowny, Edward L. (Box-folder 147: 36)
    - S (Box-folder 148: 1)
    - Schifter, Richard (Box-folder 148: 2)
    - T (Box-folder 148: 3)
    - Teller, Edward (Box-folder 148: 4)
    - V (Box-folder 148: 5)
    - W (Box-folder 148: 6)
    - Webb, James H., Jr. (Box-folder 148: 7)
    - Weinberger, Caspar (Box-folder 148: 8)
    - Wigg, David G. (Box-folder 148: 9)
    - Wiley, Marshall W. (Box-folder 148: 10)
    - Yu, Kuo-Hwa (prime minister of Taiwan) (Box-folder 148: 11)
  - 1989 alphabetical correspondence
    - A (Box-folder 148: 12)
    - B (Box-folder 148: 13)
    - Baker, James A., III (Box-folder 148: 14)
    - Bandar, Prince (Saudi Arabian ambassador) (Box-folder 148: 15)
    - Brown, Harold (Box-folder 148: 16)
    - C (Box-folder 148: 17)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box-folder 148: 18)
    - Cheney, Richard (Box-folder 148: 19)
    - D (Box-folder 148: 20)
    - Deukmejian, George (Box-folder 148: 21)
    - Drischler, Alvin Paul (Box-folder 148: 22)
    - E (Box-folder 148: 23)
    - F (Box-folder 148: 24)
    - G (Box-folder 148: 25)
    - Gaffney, Frank J., Jr. (Box-folder 148: 26)
    - H (Box-folder 148: 27)
    - Hamdoon, Nizar (Iraqi deputy foreign minister) (Box-folder 148: 28)
    - Haughey, C. J. (prime minister of Ireland) (Box-folder 148: 29)
    - I (Box-folder 148: 30)
    - J (Box-folder 148: 31)
    - K (Box-folder 148: 32)
    - Kovacevic, Livorad (Yugoslav ambassador) (Box-folder 148: 33)
    - L (Box-folder 148: 34)
    - Lane, L. W., Jr. (Box-folder 148: 35)
    - Lujan, Manuel (Box-folder 148: 36)
    - M (Box-folder 148: 37)
    - N (Box-folder 149: 1)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box-folder 149: 2)
    - O (Box-folder 149: 3)
    - P (Box-folder 149: 4)
    - Powell, Colin (Box-folder 149: 5)
    - R (Box-folder 149: 6)
    - Reagan, Ronald (Box-folder 149: 7)
    - S (Box-folder 149: 8)
    - Sabah, Sabah al-Ahmad Aljabir al- (Kuwaiti foreign minister) (Box-folder 149: 9)
    - T (Box-folder 149: 10)
    - U (Box-folder 149: 11)
    - V (Box-folder 149: 12)
    - W (Box-folder 149: 13)
  - 1990 alphabetical correspondence
    - A (Box-folder 149: 14)
    - Amis-Jessup, Jan (Box-folder 149: 15)
    - B (Box-folder 149: 16)
    - Bandar, Prince (Saudi Arabian ambassador) (Box-folder 149: 17)
    - Buckley, William F., Jr. (Box-folder 149: 18)
    - C (Box-folder 149: 19)
    - Chennault, Anna (Box-folder 149: 20)
    - D (Box-folder 149: 21)
    - Deukmejian, George (Box-folder 149: 22)
    - E (Box-folder 149: 23)
    - F (Box-folder 149: 24)
    - G (Box-folder 149: 25)
    - Gaffney, Frank J., Jr. (Box-folder 149: 26)
    - H (Box-folder 149: 27)
    - Hsu, Pei-tsun (Taiwanese defense minister) (Box-folder 149: 28)
    - I (Box-folder 149: 29)
    - J (Box-folder 149: 30)
    - K (Box-folder 149: 31)
    - Kemp, Jack (Box-folder 149: 32)
    - Kirkpatrick, Jeane J. (Box-folder 149: 33)
    - L (Box-folder 149: 34)
    - M (Box-folder 149: 35)
    - N (Box-folder 149: 36)
    - Nau, Henry R. (Box-folder 149: 37)
    - Nixon, Richard M. (Box-folder 149: 38)
    - O (Box-folder 149: 39)
    - P (Box-folder 149: 40)
    - R (Box-folder 149: 41)
    - S (Box-folder 149: 42)
    - T (Box-folder 149: 43)
    - W (Box-folder 149: 44)
    - Weinberger, Caspar (Box-folder 149: 45)
    - Z (Box-folder 149: 46)
  - 1991-2006 alphabetical correspondence
    - A (Box-folder 150: 1)
    - Armitage, Richard (Box-folder 150: 2)
    - B (Box-folder 150: 3)
    - Baker, Howard H., Jr. (Box-folder 150: 4)
    - Baker, James A., III (Box-folder 150: 5)
    - Berger, Samuel R. (Box-folder 150: 6)
    - Bush, George (Box-folder 150: 7)
    - C (Box-folder 150: 8)
    - Carter, Jimmy (Box-folder 150: 9)
    - Cheney, Richard (Box-folder 150: 10)
    - Clark, Leslie (Box-folder 150: 11)
    - Cooke, Amory J. and Phoebe Hearst (Box-folder 150: 12-14)
    - D (Box-folder 150: 15)
    - Deaver, Michael (Box-folder 150: 16)
    - Eade, Harold R. (Box-folder 150: 17)
    - Eagleburger, Lawrence (Box-folder 150: 18)
    - Erburu, Robert F. (Box-folder 151: 1)
    - G (Box-folder 151: 2)
    - Gosnell, Jack L. (Box-folder 151: 3)
    - Griles, J. Steven (Box-folder 151: 4)
    - H (Box-folder 151: 5)
    - Haig, Alexander (Box-folder 151: 6)
    - Hatch, Orrin G. (Box-folder 151: 7)
    - Herrington, John S. (Box-folder 151: 8)
    - Johnston, James D. (Box-folder 151: 9)
    - K (Box-folder 151: 10)
    - Kane, Robert F. (Box-folder 151: 11)
    - Kirkpatrick, Jeane J. (Box-folder 151: 12)
    - Kyl, Jon (Box-folder 151: 13)
    - L (Box-folder 151: 14)
    - Lake, Anthony (Box-folder 151: 15)
    - Loewenberg, Peter (Box-folder 151: 16)
    - Lungren, Daniel E. (Box-folder 151: 17)
    - M (Box-folder 151: 18)
    - Morris, Edmund (Box-folder 151: 19)
    - North, Oliver (Box-folder 151: 20)
    - Norton, Gale (Box-folder 151: 21)
    - P (Box-folder 151: 22)
    - Perot, Ross (Box-folder 152: 1)
    - Powell, Colin (Box-folder 152: 2)
    - Q (Box-folder 152: 3)
    - R (Box-folder 152: 4)
    - Reagan (Ronald) family (Box-folder 152: 5)
    - Rice, Condoleezza (Box-folder 152: 6)
    - Rumsfeld, Donald (Box-folder 152: 7)
    - S (Box-folder 152: 8)
    - Simon, William E., Jr. (Box-folder 152: 9-10)
    - Steelman, Ken E. (Box-folder 152: 11)
    - W (Box-folder 152: 12)
    - Weinberger, Caspar (Box-folder 152: 13)
    - Whittlesey, Faith Ryan (Box-folder 152: 14)
    - Wolfowitz, Paul (Box-folder 152: 15)
  - Business records
    Correspondence, memoranda, notes, reports, legal and financial documents, prospectuses, and printed matter, relating to activities of Clark as a member of the law firm of Rogers and Wells (1985-1990) and as a business consutant heading the Clark Company. Generally arranged by client
    - General
      - Rogers and Wells internal memoranda and lists, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 152: 16-17)
      - Real estate documents, 1986 (Box-folder 153: 1)
      - Correspondence, 1985 (Box-folder 153: 2)
      - Miscellany, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 153: 3)
    - ABB Combustion Engineering Nuclear Systems
      Includes material on nuclear power plant operations in Taiwan
      - 1990-1991 (Box-folder 153: 4)
      - 1992-1994 (Box-folder 153: 5)
      - 1995 (Box-folder 153: 6)
      - 1996-1997 (Box-folder 153: 7)
    - Boeing Company
      Includes material on aircraft sales to Taiwan and South Korea
      - 1985-1986 (Box-folder 154: 1)
      - 1987-1989 (Box-folder 154: 2)
      - 1990-1994 (Box-folder 154: 3)
      - 1995 (Box-folder 154: 4-5)
      - 1996 (Box-folder 154: 6, Box-folder 155: 1)
      - 1997 (Box-folder 155: 2)
      - 1998 (Box-folder 156: 1, Box-folder 155: 3-4)
      - 1999 (Box-folder 156: 2-3)
      - 2000 (Box-folder 156: 4, Box-folder 157: 1-2)
      - 2001 (Box-folder 157: 3-4)
      - 2002 (Box-folder 157: 5, Box-folder 158: 1)
      - 2003 (Box-folder 158: 2)
      - 2004 (Box-folder 158: 3-5)
      - 2005 (Box-folder 158: 6, Box-folder 159: 1)
      - 2006 (Box-folder 159: 2)
    - Braun and Company, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 159: 3-4)
      Includes material on promotion of American business opportunities in Morocco and Austria
    - Brown and Bryant, Inc., 1988 (Box-folder 159: 5)
      Relates to insurance settlement in litigation involving the Environmental Protection Agency
    - California Biotechnology, Inc., 1985-1988 (Box-folder 160: 1)
      Clark was a director of the company
    - Celeron Corporation, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 160: 2)
      Relates to oil pipeline proposals
    - Citicorp, 1985 (Box-folder 160: 3)
      Relates to California Assembly legislation affecting the company
    - Coastal Corporation, 1987 (Box-folder 160: 4)
      Relates to compliance with U.S. government pipeline regulations
    - Cooper Companies, Inc., 1988 (Box-folder 160: 5)
    - Davis Walker Corporation, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 160: 6)
      Relates to Canadian wire product competition and to proposed company joint venture with China
    - Dow Chemical Company, 1987 (Box-folder 160: 7)
      Relates to sale of Freeport, Texas petroleum refinery to a Saudi Arabian concern
    - E. and J. Gallo Winery, 1986 (Box-folder 160: 8)
      Relates to proposed federal excise tax on wine
    - E. F. Hutton and Company, 1985 (Box-folder 160: 9)
      Relates to federal charges of fraud against the company
    - Energy World Trade, Inc., 1985-1987 (Box-folder 161: 1-2)
      Relates to oil production in Iraq and elsewhere. See also Iraq/Aqaba Pipeline Project
    - Fluor Corporation, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 161: 3)
      Relates to cooperation with Saudi Arabaia in oil production ventures. See also Iraq/Aqaba Pipeline Project
    - GST Telecommunications, Inc., 1996-1997 (Box-folder 161: 4)
      Includes material on telecommunications operations in Mexico
    - Grupo PYCSA (Mexican firm), 1996 (Box-folder 161: 5)
      Includes material on proposed highway construction in Mexico
    - IDC Communications, Inc., 1995 (Box-folder 161: 6)
      Relates to telecommunications in Mexico
    - Iraq/Aqaba Pipeline Project
      Relates to proposed oil pipeline from Iraq to Aqaba, Jordan, to be undertaken by a company to be formed from private interests and the government of Jordan. Includes inputs from governments of Iraq, Israel, Saudi Arabia and the United States
      - 1985 (Box-folder 162: 1-2)
      - 1986 (Box-folder 162: 3)
      - 1987 (Box-folder 162: 4)
      - 1988 (Box-folder 162: 5)
    - JBS Telecom, Inc., 1995 (Box-folder 162: 6)
    - Lockheed Company, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 162: 7)
      Relates to aircraft sales to South Korea and elsewhere. Includes material on 1972 sales to Libya
    - Lucas International, Inc., 1994-1997 (Box-folder 162: 8)
    - McCann FitzGerald Solicitors (Irish law firm), 1993-1999 (Box-folder 163: 1)
    - Malahide Secretarial Services (Irish firm), 1993-2000 (Box-folder 163: 2)
    - Mexican Energy Initiative (investment proposal), 1999-2000 (Box-folder 163: 3)
    - Microgistics, Inc., 1998 (Box-folder 163: 4)